Even bigger than you imagined
Andre the Giant is a documentary film directed by Jason Hehir.
An ambitious and wide-ranging documentary exploring Andre’s upbringing in France, his
celebrated career in WWE, and his forays in the entertainment world.
Self (archive footage), played by André Roussimoff.
Self, played by Hulk Hogan.
Self, played by Arnold Schwarzenegger.
Self, played by Vince McMahon.
Self, played by Ric Flair.
Self, played by Gene Okerlund.
André the Giant is a 2018 American documentary film based on the life of French
professional wrestler and actor André René Roussimoff, best known as André the Giant.
The documentary covers André's life with gigantism.
The film features professional wrestlers and media personalities such as Vince McMahon, Hulk Hogan, Pat Patterson, Tim White,
Ric Flair, Dave Meltzer, Arnold Schwarzenegger, Billy Crystal as well as family members discussing André's life.
André the Giant was released on HBO on April 10, 2018.
The film was executively produced by Janine Marmot and Bill Simmons, who had
been interested in creating a documentary on André previously.
The documentary was slated as focusing on his "upbringing in France, his
celebrated career in WWE and his forays in the entertainment world".
The film explores themes of wrestling, biography, pro wrestling, sport.